

PROFILE

I am an undergraduate graduate of Environmental Engineering from 2015 -2022. Successfully completed college in 7 years. Served as post-training chairman for 3 months.

Want to improve my skills and knowledge by joining MERN Web Developer bootcamp. Experienced in creating web using ReactJS, Bootsrap, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, and MongoDB. Mastering the JavaScript programming language.

CONTACT

PHONE: 082283612770

WEBSITE:

ECOMMERCE WEB'S:

https://github.com/alifgunadi/MERN.git

PORTOFOLIO:

https://alifgunadi--unique-trifle-627819.netlify.app/index.html
CHAT AI DISCORD BOT:

https://github.com/alifgunadi/v14.git

EMAIL:

alifgunadi1303@gmail.com

SOCIAL LINK

<u>Linkedin</u>: Muhammad Alif Gunadi <u>Github</u>: alifgunadi

MUHAMMAD ALIF GUNADI

WEB DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

Eduwork

Jan 2023 – April 2023 Mern Full Stack Developer Bootcamp

Institute Technology National Bandung

Oct 2015 – Sept 2022 Environmental Engineering

EXPERIENCE

Environmental Engineering Student Association Chief Executive Officer Post Training

May 2017 – Aug 2017 4 Month event implementation

PT. Semen Padang. HSE (Health, Safety, and Environment) Jun 2018 – Jul 2018

1-month internship.

SKILLS

